var quiz = [{"answers": ["Chlorine", "All of the choices are true", "Fluorine", "Cryptosporidium"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "All of the following have been implicated as contaminant dangers in tap water, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The bottled water industry is susceptible to greenwashing."}, {"answers": ["1950s", "1990s", "1900s", "1850s"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "When did bottled water consumption rapidly begin to increase?"}, {"answers": ["perceptual scarcity", "hydrological scarcity", "induced scarcity", "techno-economic scarcity"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Which type of water scarcity involves a lack of water due to inadequate infrastructure from underdevelopment?"}, {"answers": ["hydrological", "perceptual", "techno-economic", "none of the choices is correct"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The type of water scarcity that is most prevalent in the United States is _______."}, {"answers": ["green certification program", "commodity cycle", "life cycle analysis", "risk assessment"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "A _______ can be used to determine the environmental impact of a product through all stages of production and consumption."}, {"answers": ["USGS", "NTWD", "EPA", "FDA"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which government agency in the United States oversees municipal water?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Industrialized nations use less water per capita than less developed countries."}, {"answers": ["2014", "2034", "2025", "2055"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "According to the United Nations, two-thirds of the world\u2019s population may be living in water-stressed countries by what year?"}, {"answers": ["All of the choices involve the use of oil", "Production to fill, seal and label bottles", "Making the plastic for the bottles", "Transportation from water supply"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Oil is used in all of the following phases of the life cycle of bottled water, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["risk assessment", "risk communication", "risk perception", "green washing"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "If a municipal water utility plant wanted to convey information about the safety of tap water, this would be an example of what?"}, {"answers": ["So much water is removed from local streams to bottle water that many are now dry.", "There are too many choices of bottled drinks.", "Water is bottled faster than it can be consumed.", "That bottled water has become a commodity."], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "An example of overproduction as it related to bottled drink choices is:"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Ounce for ounce, bottled water is more costly than oil."}, {"answers": ["Industrial pollutants", "Agricultural pollutants", "Naturally occurring pollutants", "Water treatment by-product pollutants"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "According to the National Tap Water Database, the overall report for Michigan has found that the largest source of pollutants in our state comes from what source?   See link: http://www.ewg.org/tap-water/MichiganDrinkingWaterQualityReport/"}, {"answers": ["commodity; flow resource", "none of the choices is correct", "common resource; commodity", "stock resource; commodity"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Water has traditionally been seen as a _______, but has increasingly been privatized and sold as a _______."}, {"answers": ["perceptual scarcity", "hydrological scarcity", "induced scarcity", "techno-economic scarcity"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which type of water scarcity involves a lack of water due to climatological and geographical factors?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Over the course of\u00a0 15 years, some people spend as much on bottled water as the purchase of a decent sized home."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Tap water is potentially safer than bottled water because it is more strictly regulated."}, {"answers": ["100%", "40%", "10%", "80%"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "According to the notes, what percentage of plastic bottles are thrown away?"}, {"answers": ["primitive accumulation", "overproduction", "green washing", "eutrophication"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The Nestl\u00e9 Corporation seized public water resources in Mecosta County, Michigan in order to bottle and sell the water.\u00a0 This process is known as _______."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The rise of the bottled water industry was simultaneous with increasing privatization of municipal water supplies."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Desalinization\u00a0 is an affordable way to increase water supplies."}, {"answers": ["induced scarcity", "techno-economic scarcity", "perceptual scarcity", "hydrological scarcity"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which type of water scarcity involves a belief that existing water supplies are scarce or hazardous?"}, {"answers": ["Local water supplies are often associated with the wealthy only", "Local water supplies are often privatized", "Local water supplies are often scarce", "Local water supplies are often polluted"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "In underdeveloped countries, bottled water is used to replace water supplies that can be all of the following, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["techno-economic scarcity", "perceptual scarcity", "induced scarcity", "hydrological scarcity"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Which type of water scarcity mostly affects desert regions?"}, {"answers": ["Aquafina", "Ice Mountain", "Desani", "Polar Springs"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The people of Mecosta County, MI, protested appropriation of groundwater by    Nestl\u00e9 in order to produce which brand of bottled water?"}, {"answers": ["green washing", "commodity pricing", "primitive accumulation", "over production"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "When water is appropriated from natural or public sources and then sold back to the community at a marked up price, this is called:"}, {"answers": ["Through taste tests that have shown that bottled water often does taste better than tap.", "By purchasing land and water rights in their communities, thereby limiting choice.", "By successfully educating the public on the safety of bottled water over tap water.", "Through successful marketing and packaging."], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "How are bottle water companies able to get affluent people to purchase water they could otherwise get for free?"}, {"answers": ["none of the other choices is correct", "a wealthy city in Saudi Arabia", "New York City", "a rapidly growing city in South Africa"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "In which location are you most likely to find techno-economic scarcity?"}, {"answers": ["Most bottled water is packaged tap water.", "In the U.S., tap water is more strictly regulated than bottled water.", "Bottled water appears to be replacing soft drink consumption as a healthier trend.", "No bottled water companies have adopted public water safety standards."], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "All of the following statements concerning bottled water and tap water are true, EXCEPT:"}]

quizCollection['15'] = quiz